veenaworld.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Veena World

Veena Patil Hospitality Private Limited (hereinafter referred as “Veena World”, “we”, “us” or “our”) understands and respects the importance of privacy of its users (hereinafter referred as “You” or “Your”). This Privacy Policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from You, or that You provide us, via the website https://www.veenaworld.com (hereinafter referred as “the website”) will be processed by us. Confidentiality of information provided by You will be maintained. Veena World includes its Subsidiary Companies. will be processed by us. Confidentiality of information provided by You will be maintained. Veena World includes its Subsidiary Companies. 

This Privacy Policy is applicable to any person/s who book/purchase/intend to purchase/enquire about any product(s) and/or service(s) made available by Veena World through its website as well as offices including corporate office, branch offices and preferred sales partners. By making a booking/purchase or submitting Your personal data via the website or any offices, You agree to the transfer, storing or processing of such information. If You do not agree to Veena World’s use of Your personal data we cannot accept Your booking and You should not use the website. 

You may be asked for personal information including but not limited to name, address, email address, telephone number, date of birth, credit/debit card number (in encrypted form) with expiration date, banking details, Aadhar Details, PAN Details, Visa related Documents (photographs, Bank Details, Business/Company Details, etc), Passport Details (passport number, issue date, expiry date), mobile number, Professional Qualifications/details, etc., anytime while making a booking/purchase via the website or any other customer touch points. We may keep a record of Your email or other correspondence, and if You call us by telephone, we may monitor and/or record phone conversations for training and customer service reasons. We may collect details of Your computer and visits to this Site (including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, IP address, operating system and browser type) for system administration purposes and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. 

In some cases we may also need to collect more sensitive personal data such as information regarding Your medical conditions, disabilities and special requirements along with medical Certificates supporting the same. This information is allowed to be stored by You and is collected in order to arrange for the services You are requesting and this Information is presented to You at the time of making a booking/purchase so that the process of bookings /purchase is completed expeditiously. This Information may also be used internally for research, analysis and auditing.Cookies and other information may be used to optimize the viewing experience, troubleshoot any problems and serve better content. 

The predominant purpose in collecting, storing, transferring or sharing the information is to: 

  * Communicate with You regarding bookings/purchase; 
  * Send booking confirmations; 
  * Keep You updated regarding transaction status; 
  * Sending tour related information on daily basis; 
  * Send verification/alert message(s) or email(s). 
  * Notify and update the changes in bookings. 
  * Resolve complaints and disputes. 
  * Allow our customer service department to contact You. 
  * Detecting and prevent fraudulent or criminal activity. 
  * Carry out our obligations arising in connection with any contracts entered into between You and us, or between You and a third party supplier; 
  * Ensure that content from the website is presented in the most effective manner for You; 

This Site uses cookies to distinguish You from other users. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by Your browser on Your device's hard drive when You visit the website. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. You can control and delete how and whether cookies will be accepted by Your browser by changing the options on Your web browser or using certain software programs but disabling them may affect the functionality of this website. Once You access the website, You consent to our use of cookies. Some of these cookies are essential to make the website user friendly and work properly, to allow You to make Your booking/purchases, and to enable us to serve You better and more efficiently. Other types of cookies help us to provide You with a good experience when You browse our Site, and also allow us to improve our Site or the way we provide our service to customers. No Personal Information is collected during this process. The information so collected during this process, is anonymous, and does not link online actions to You.

We may record anonymous, non-personal information (not including Your name, address, email address or telephone number) about Your visits to this and other web sites in order to measure advertising effectiveness. We may also collect non personal information about Your visit to our website, based on Your browsing (click stream) activities. This information may include the pages browsed and products and services viewed or booked for example. None of this information is passed to any third party, and is used solely by us to provide You with a better user experience on the Website.

In order to manage and develop our offers and to provide You with better products and services tailored to Your individual interests and needs, we may also use cookies to display any advertisement to You while You are on the Website or to send You offers via e-mails focusing particularly on destinations which may be of Your interest. The third party advertising companies may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of the advertisements. All such information is anonymous. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is an industry standard technology and is used by all major websites. They may use this anonymous information about Your visits to the Website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to You.

Some information that You should have about Cookies:

  * Certain features on the website are only available through the use of cookies. 
  * Cookies allow You to log in without having to type Your login name each time (only Your password is needed) and identify the User and maintain their signed-in status. 
  * Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from the User’s hard drive at the end of a session. “Persistent cookies” remain in place across multiple visits to our websites. 
  * You are free to decline the cookies if their browser permits, although doing so may interfere with use of the website. 

We may use Cookies to:

  * Measure the entry and exit points of visitors to the Site and respective number of visitors to various pages and sections of the Site and details of searches performed. 
  * Measure the usage of advertising banners and other click through from the Site. 
  * Understand and analyse trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behaviour on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 
  * We may use this information in our marketing and advertising services. 
  * Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether the mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.
